<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2020-2025 The ScummVM Team -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.scummvm.scummvm</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>ScummVM</name>
  <summary>Interpreter for numerous adventure games and role-playing games</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">مترجم للعديد من ألعاب المغامرات ولعب الأدوار</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="be-tarask">Інтэрпрэтатар многіх авантурных і ролявых гульняў</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Intèrpret per a nombrosos jocs d'aventura i jocs de rol</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Interpreter für zahlreiche Adventure-Spiele und RPGs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Intérprete de numerosas aventuras gráficas y RPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Pelitulkki lukuisille seikkailu- ja roolipeleille</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Interpréteur pour de nombreux jeux d'aventure et jeux de rôle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">מפרש עבור מספר גדול של משחקי הרפתקאות ומשחקי תפקידים</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Interpreter számos kalandjátékhoz és szerepjátékhoz</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Interprete per numerosi giochi di avventura e di ruolo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">数多くのアドベンチャーゲームやロールプレイングゲームの通訳</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">여러 어드벤처 게임과 RPG를 위한 인터프리터</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nb">Programvaretolk for utallige eventyr- og rollespill</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Interpreter voor diverse adventure spellen en rollenspellen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Interpreter wielu gier przygodowych oraz RPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Interpretador para vários jogos de aventura e RPG</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-PT">Interpretador de vários jogos de aventura e RPGs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Интерпретатор множества приключенческих и ролевых игр</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Інтерпретатор для численних пригодницьких і рольових ігор</summary>
  <developer_name>The ScummVM Team</developer_name>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.scummvm.scummvm.desktop</launchable>
  <provides>
    <binary>scummvm</binary>
  </provides>
  <description>
    <p>
      ScummVM is a program which allows you to run a wide variety of classic
      graphical point-and-click adventure games and role-playing games,
      provided you already have their data files. The clever part about this:
      ScummVM just replaces the executables shipped with the game,
      allowing you to play them on systems for which they were never designed!
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">ScummVM هو برنامج يسمح لك بتشغيل مجموعة متنوعة من ألعاب المغامرات وألعاب
تقمص الأدوار الرسومية والتأشير والنقر ، بشرط أن يكون لديك بالفعل ملفات
البيانات الخاصة بهم. الجزء الذكي في هذا الأمر: يستبدل ScummVM الملفات
التنفيذية التي يتم شحنها مع اللعبة ، مما يتيح لك تشغيلها على أنظمة لم يتم
تصميمها من أجلها مطلقًا!</p>
    <p xml:lang="be-tarask">ScummVM — гэта праграма для запуску розных клясічных графічных point-and-
click авантурных і ралявых гульняў, пры ўмове, што вы маеце зьвесткі тых
гульняў. Карацей, ScummVM проста замяняе выканальныя файлы гульняў,
дазваляючы гуляць на сістэмах, на якія іх ніколі не распрацоўвалі!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">ScummVM és un programa que permet executar una àmplia varietat de jocs
clàssics d'aventures gràfiques «point-and-click» i jocs de rol, sempre que
ja tingueu els seus fitxers de dades. La part intel·ligent sobre això:
ScummVM només substitueix els executables originals del joc, permetent-vos
jugar-los en sistemes per als quals mai van ser dissenyats!</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">ScummVM ist ein Programm, welches dir ermöglicht, zahlreiche Adventures und
RPGs auszuführen, vorausgesetzt, du bist im Besitz der passenden
Spieldateien. ScummVM ersetzt dabei die ausführbaren Programmdateien, die
ursprünglich mit dem Spiel mitgeliefert wurden. Dadurch können diese Spiele
auf Systemen gespielt werden, für welche sie nie entwickelt wurden!</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το ScummVM είναι μια εφαρμογή που σας επιτρέπει να παίξετε μια ευρεία
ποικιλία από κλασσικά παιχνίδια περιπέτειας point-and-click, και ρόλων
(adventure και role-playing), αρκεί να έχετε στην κατοχή σας τα αρχεία
δεδομένων τους. Το ενδιαφέρον σε αυτή την υπόθεση είναι το εξής: το ScummVM
απλά αντικαθιστά τα εκτελέσιμα που συνόδευαν τα παιχνίδια, επιτρέποντάς σας
να τα παίξετε σε συστήματα για τα οποία δεν είχαν σχεδιαστεί ποτέ!</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">ScummVM es un programa que te permite ejecutar una amplia selección de
aventuras gráficas «point-and-click» y RPG clásicos, siempre y cuando ya
tengas sus archivos de datos. Lo interesante es que ScummVM se limita a
sustituir los ejecutables de cada juego, ¡lo que permite jugarlos en
sistemas para los que nunca fueron diseñados!</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">ScummVM on ohjelma jonka avulla voit pelata lukuisia klassisia graafisia
seikkailu- ja roolipelejä, olettaen että sinulla on jo pelien datatiedostot.
Tämä on fiksua koska: ScummVM korvaa itse ajettavan peliohjelman, joten voit
pelata pelejä jopa alustoilla joille pelejä ei koskaan suunniteltu!</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">ScummVM est un programme qui vous permet d'exécuter une grande variété de
jeux d'aventure graphique point-and-click et de jeux de rôle, à condition
que vous ayez déjà leurs fichiers de données. Ce qui est génial dans tout
ça : ScummVM remplace simplement les exécutables livrés avec les jeux, ce
qui vous permet de jouer sur des systèmes pour lesquels ces jeux n'ont
jamais été conçus !</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">ScummVM הינה תכנה שמאפשרת להריץ מגוון רחב של משחקי הרפתקאות גרפיים הצבע-
והקלק ומשחקי תפקידים, בהינתן קבצי הנתונים שלהם. החלק המעניין הוא: ScummVM
מחליפה רק את קובץ הריצה שהגיע עם המשחק, מה שמאפשר לשחק בהם על מערכות אליהם
המשחק מעולם לא תוכנן!</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A ScummVM egy olyan program, mely számos klasszikus grafikus point-and-click
kalandjáték és szerepjáték futtatását teszi lehetővé, feltéve, hogy már
rendelkeznek az adatfájljaikkal. Az okos rész ebben: A ScummVM csak
kicseréli a játékkal szállított futtatható fájlokat, lehetővé téve számukra,
hogy olyan rendszereken játsszák őket, amelyekre soha nem lettek tervezve!</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">ScummVM è un programma che permette di eseguire svariate avventure grafiche
e giochi di ruolo classici, a patto di averne a disposizione i files
originali. Il bello è che ScummVM sostituisce gli eseguibili originari,
permettendo di eseguire i giochi su piattaforme per cui non erano neppure
mai stati pensati!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">ScummVMは、データファイルが既にある場合に、さまざまな古典的なグラフィカルポイ
ントアンドクリックアドベンチャーゲームやロールプレイングゲームを実行できるよ
うにするプログラムです。これに関する巧妙な部分：ScummVMは、ゲームに付属してい
る実行可能ファイルを置き換えるだけなので、設計されたことのないシステムで実行
できます!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">ScummVM은 데이터 파일을 가진 경우 다양한 고전 그래픽 포인트 앤 클릭 어드벤처
게임과 롤플레잉 게임을 실행할 수 있게 하는 프로그램입니다. ScummVM은 게임과
함께 제공된 실행파일을 대체하기 때문에 원래 게임이 실행되도록 설계되지 않은
시스템에서도 실행할 수 있습니다!</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">ScummVM er et program som lar deg kjøre et bredt assortiment av klassiske
pek-og-klikk-eventyrspill og rollespill – forutsatt at du allerede har
datafilene til spillet. Det finurlige med det hele er at ScummVM kun
erstatter selve programdelen av spillet og gjør det slik at du kan spille
det på plattformer det aldri var utviklet til å kjøre på!</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">ScummVM is een programma die het mogelijk maakt om een grote verscheidenheid
aan klassieke grafische point-and-click adventure spellen en rollenspellen
te spelen, mits je de benodigde data bestanden al hebt. Het unieke hiervan
is: ScummVM vervangt de executables die bij het spel geleverd worden,
waardoor je ze kan spelen op systemen waar ze niet voor waren gemaakt!</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">ScummVM to program pozwalający na uruchomienie bogatego wyboru klasycznych
graficznych gier przygodowych typu „wskaż i kliknij”, oraz gier RPG - pod
warunkiem posiadania ich danych. ScummVM podmienia oryginalny program gier,
pozwalając na granie w nie na systemach, na które nigdy nie były napisane!</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">ScummVM é um programa que permite que você execute uma ampla variedade de
jogos clássicos de point-and-click (apontar e clicar) e RPG, desde que você
já tenha seus arquivos de dados. A melhor parte: ScummVM apenas substitui os
executáveis do jogo, permitindo que você os jogue em sistemas para os quais
eles nunca foram projetados!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">ScummVM - это программа, которая позволяет запускать широкий спектр
классических графических приключенческих игр и ролевых игр, при условии, что
у вас уже есть их файлы данных. Самое умное в этом: ScummVM просто заменяет
исполняемые файлы, поставляемые с игрой, позволяя вам играть в них на
системах, для которых они никогда не были разработаны!</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">ScummVM - це програма, яка дозволяє запускати широкий спектр класичних
графічних пригодницьких ігор та рольових ігор, якщо у вас вже є їх файли
даних. Щонайголовніше: ScummVM просто замінює виконувані файли, що
постачаються разом із грою, дозволяючи відтворювати їх у системах, для яких
вони ніколи не були розроблені!</p>
    <p>
      Currently, ScummVM supports a huge library of adventures with over 250 games in total.
      It supports many classics published by legendary studios like LucasArts, Sierra On-Line,
      Revolution Software, Cyan, Inc. and Westwood Studios.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">حاليًا ، تدعم ScummVM مكتبة ضخمة من المغامرات تضم أكثر من 4000 لعبة في
المجموع. وهو يدعم العديد من الكلاسيكيات التي نشرتها الاستوديوهات الأسطورية
مثل LucasArts و Sierra On-Line و Revolution Software و Cyan، Inc. و Westwood
Studios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="be-tarask">На гэты момант ScummVM падтрымлівае вялічэзную бібліятэку авантур, дзе болей
за 4000 гульняў. Вы зможаце дакрануцца да многіх клясічных твораў, выданых
леґэндарнымі студыямі як LucasArts, Sierra On-Line, Revolution Software,
Cyan, Inc. і Westwood Studios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Actualment, ScummVM suporta una enorme biblioteca d'aventures amb més de
4.000 jocs en total. Dóna suport a molts clàssics publicats per estudis
llegendaris com LucasArts, Sierra On-Line, Revolution Software, Cyan, Inc. i
Westwood Studios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Aktuell unterstützt ScummVM eine umfangreiche Bibliothek von Adventure-
Spielen mit insgesamt über 4000 Spielen. Unterstützt werden viele Klassiker,
die von legendären Studios wie LucasArts, Sierra On-Line, Revolution
Software, Cyan Inc. und den Westwood Studios entwickelt wurden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το ScummVM υποστηρίζει μια τεράστια βιβλιοθήκη από παιχνίδια περιπέτειας
(adventure games) με περισσότερους από 4000 τίτλους συνολικά. Υποστηρίζει
πολλούς από τους κλασσικούς τίτλους που έχουν εκδώσει θρυλικά στούντιο όπως
οι LucasArts, Sierra On-Line, Revolution Software, Cyan, Inc. και Westwood
Studios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">ScummVM es compatible con una inmensa biblioteca de más de 4 000 juegos en
total. Funciona con muchos de los clásicos publicados por estudios
legendarios como LucasArts, Sierra On-Line, Revolution Software, Cyan, Inc.
y Westwood Studios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Tällä hetkellä ScummVM tukee jättimäistä seikkailujen kirjastoa, kaikkiaan
yli 4000 peliä. Se tukee lukuisia klassikkoja legendaarisilta studioilta
kuten LucasArts, Sierra On-Line, Revolution Software, Cyan, Inc. ja Westwood
Studios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Actuellement, ScummVM supporte une énorme collection d'aventures avec plus
de 4000 jeux au total. Il prend en charge de nombreux classiques publiés par
des studios légendaires comme LucasArts, Sierra On-Line, Revolution
Software, Cyan, Inc. et Westwood Studios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">נכון להיום, ScummVM תומכת בספריה ענקית של הרפתקאות, עם למעלה מ-4000 משחקים
בסך הכל. ביניהם מיטב הקלאסיקות של אולפנים אגדיים כמו LucasArts, Sierra On-
Line, Revolution Software, Cyan, Inc. וגם Westwood Studios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Jelenleg a ScummVM egy hatalmas kalandkönyvtárat támogat, összesen több mint
4000 játékkal. Támogatja számos legendás stúdió által kiadott klasszikust,
mint például a LucasArts, a Sierra On-Line, a Revolution Software, a Cyan,
Inc. és a Westwood Studios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Attualmente, ScummVM supporta una vastissima collezione di giochi di
avventura, per un totale di oltre 4000 titoli. Tra questi, molti giochi
rinomati pubblicati da editori leggendari come la LucasArts, la Sierra On-
Line, la Revolution Software, la Cyan, Inc. o i Westwood Studios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">現在、ScummVMは、合計4000を超えるゲームを備えた膨大なアドベンチャーライブラリ
をサポートしています。 LucasArts、Sierra On-Line、Revolution Software、Cyan、
Inc.、WestwoodStudiosなどの伝説的なスタジオによって公開された多くのクラシック
をサポートしています.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">현재 ScummVM은 합계 4000개를 넘는 수많은 어드벤처 게임을 지원합니다.
LucasArts, Sierra On-Line, Revolution Software, Cyan, Inc., 그리고 Westwood
Studios 같은 전설적인 스튜디오에서 발표된 많은 고전을 지원합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">For øyeblikket støtter ScummVM et eventyrlig bibliotek på over 4000
spilltitler totalt. Det støtter mange klassikere utgitt av legendariske
spillstudioer som bl.a. LucasArts, Sierra On-Line, Revolution Software,
Cyan, Inc. og Westwood Studios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Momenteel ondersteunt ScummVM een enorme hoeveelheid adventures van meer dan
4000 spellen in totaal. Het ondersteunt vele klassiekers gepubliceerd door
legendarische studios als LucasArts, Sierra On-Line, Revolution Software,
Cyan, Inc. en Westwood Studios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Obecnie ScummVM obsługuje wielki katalog przygód liczący razem ponad 4000
gier. Obsługuje wiele klasycznych gier wydanych przez legandarne studia
takie jak LucasArts, Sierra On-Line, Revolution Software, Cyan, Inc. oraz
Westwood Studios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Atualmente o ScummVM suporta uma enorme biblioteca de aventuras com mais de
4000 jogos no total. Ele suporta muitos clássicos publicados por estúdios
lendários como LucasArts, Sierra On-Line, Revolution Software, Cyan, Inc. e
Westwood Studios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">В настоящее время ScummVM поддерживает огромную библиотеку приключений,
насчитывающую в общей сложности более 4000 игр. Он поддерживает множество
классических произведений, выпущенных легендарными студиями, такими как
LucasArts, Sierra On-Line, Revolution Software, Cyan, Inc. и Westwood
Studios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">В даний час ScummVM підтримує величезну бібліотеку пригодницьких ігор із
загальною кількістю понад 4000. Проект підтримує багато класичних творів,
опублікованих такими легендарними студіями, як LucasArts, Sierra On-Line,
Revolution Software, Cyan, Inc. та Westwood Studios.</p>
    <p>
      Next to ground-breaking titles like the Monkey Island series, Broken Sword,
      Myst, Blade Runner and countless other games you will find
      some really obscure adventures and truly hidden gems to explore.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">بجانب العناوين الرائدة مثل سلسلة Monkey Island و Broken Sword و Myst و Blade
Runner وعدد لا يحصى من الألعاب الأخرى ، ستجد بعض المغامرات الغامضة حقًا
والأحجار الكريمة المخفية حقًا لاستكشافها.</p>
    <p xml:lang="be-tarask">Разам з рэвалюцыйнымі гульнямі як Monkey Island, Broken Sword, Myst, Blade
Runner і безьлічам іншых гульняў, вы знойдзіце насамрэч малавядомыя авантуры
й прыхаваныя скарбы.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Al costat de títols innovadors com la sèrie Monkey Island, Broken Sword,
Myst, Blade Runner i molts altres jocs trobareu algunes aventures realment
fosques i altres gemmes realment ocultes per explorar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Neben bahnbrechenden Titel wie der Monkey Island-Serie, Baphomets Fluch,
Myst, Blade Runner und zahllosen weiteren Spielen wirst du auch einige
wirklich kuriose Adventures und versteckte Schätze entdecken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Μαζί με καινοτόμους για την εποχή τους τίτλους, όπως ήταν οι σειρές Monkey
Island, Broken Sword, Myst, Blade Runner και αμέτρητα άλλα παιχνίδια, θα
βρείτε και μερικούς σχετικά άγνωστους τίτλους περιπέτειας και πραγματικά
κρυμμένα διαμαντάκια για να εξερευνήσετε.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Podrás jugar a títulos tan innovadores como las sagas de Monkey Island,
Broken Sword, Myst, Blade Runner como aventuras menos conocidas y otras
joyas ocultas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Uraauurtaneiden Monkey Island-, Broken Sword-, Myst-, Blade Runner- ja
lukuisten muiden pelien ohelta löydät myös vähemmän tunnettuja helmiä
tutkittavaksesi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">À côté de titres révolutionnaires comme la série Monkey Island, Broken Sword
(Les Chevaliers de Baphomet) , Myst, Blade Runner et d'innombrables autres
jeux, vous trouverez des aventures vraiment obscures et des pépites vraiment
bien cachées à explorer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">לצד כותרים פורצי דרך כמו סדרת אי הקופים, חרב שבורה, Myst, בלייד ראנר
ואינספור משחקים נוספים תוכלו למצוא גם הרפתקאות עמומות ופנינות נסתרות של ממש
שמחכות שתגלו אותן.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Az olyan úttörő címek mellett, mint a Monkey Island sorozat, a Broken Sword,
a Myst, a Blade Runner és számtalan más játék, valóban homályos kalandokat
és valóban rejtett drágaköveket találhat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Pietre miliari come la saga di Monkey Island, Broken Sword, Myst, Blade
Runner e innumerevoli altri titoli tutti da scoprire. Potrai trovare
avventure sconosciute ai più ma anche dei gioiellini ingiustamente
dimenticati.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">モンキーアイランドシリーズ、ブロークンソード、ミスト、ブレードランナー、その
他の無数のゲームなどの画期的なタイトルの横に、いくつかの本当にあいまいな冒険
と真に隠された宝石を見つけることができます.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Monkey Island 시리즈, Broken Sword, Myst, Blade Runner와 같이 획기적인 타이틀
을 비롯해, 잘 알려지지 않은 어드벤처 게임과 진정한 숨겨진 보석을 찾아볼 수 있
습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nb">Sammen med banebrytende titler som Monkey Island-serien, Broken Sword, Myst,
Blade Runner og utallige andre spill finner du også enkelte kuriositeter og
skjulte skatter det kan være verdt å gi et forsøk.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Naast spraakmakende titels zoals de Monkey Island series, Broken Sword,
Myst, Blade Runner en talloze andere spellen zal je enkele vage adventures
vinden en echte verborgen pareltjes ontdekken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Poza przełomowymi tytułami, takimi jak seria Monkey Island, Broken Sword,
Myst, Blade Runner i wieloma innymi, znajdziesz tu również wiele mało
znanych przygód i naprawdę mało znanych perełek.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Ao lado de títulos inovadores como a série Monkey Island, Broken Sword,
Myst, Blade Runner e inúmeros outros jogos, você encontrará algumas
aventuras realmente obscuras e verdadeiras joias raras para explorar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Наряду с новаторскими играми, такими как серия Monkey Island, Broken Sword,
Myst, Blade Runner и бесчисленное множество других игр, вы найдете
действительно малоизвестные приключения и действительно скрытые сокровища
для исследования.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Окрім новаторських ігор, як-от серії Monkey Island, Broken Sword, Myst,
Blade Runner та незліченної кількості інших, ви знайдете декілька справді
маловідомих пригодницьких ігор та справді прихованих дорогоцінних каменів,
які слід дослідити.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.scummvm.org/frs/extras/storefront/screenshots/screenshot_1.png</image>
      <caption>ScummVM Launcher</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.scummvm.org/frs/extras/storefront/screenshots/screenshot_2.png</image>
      <caption>ScummVM running 'Flight of the Amazon Queen'</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.scummvm.org/frs/extras/storefront/screenshots/screenshot_3.png</image>
      <caption>ScummVM running 'Beneath a Steel Sky'</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.scummvm.org/frs/extras/storefront/screenshots/screenshot_4.png</image>
      <caption>ScummVM running 'The Curse of Monkey Island'</caption>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://www.scummvm.org/frs/extras/storefront/screenshots/screenshot_5.png</image>
      <caption>ScummVM running a demo of 'Myst'</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.scummvm.org</url>
  <update_contact>scummvm-devel@lists.scummvm.org</update_contact>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-desecration">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-slavery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-worship">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-homosexuality">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-prostitution">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-adultery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-appearance">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>
